In the game of seduction there are no rules.
The Seductress is a drama, romance, thriller film directed by J. Edie Martin.
Alexis Baxter marries and murders wealthy men in order to assume their fortune.
Alexis Baxter, played by Shauna O'Brien.
Kay Sanders, played by Gabriella Hall.
Paul Morton (as Jonathan Smith), played by Jarod Carey.
Roman Jurow (as Gary Angelino), played by Vince Vouyer.
Brandis Baxter, played by Morgan Moran.
Lewis Stone, played by Sid Fontana.
Cree Summer Francks (born July 7, 1969) is an
American-Canadian actress and singer.
In animation, she has voiced characters such as Elmyra Duff in Tiny Toon Adventures and
related media, Susie Carmichael in Rugrats and Lizard in Spirit Rangers.
The latter two respectively won her an NAACP Image Award and two
nominations at the Children's and Family Emmy Awards.
Summer is also known for her roles in Inspector Gadget, Batman Beyond, Horrible Histories, Clifford the Big Red Dog, Codename: Kids Next Door, Atlantis: The
Lost Empire, Danny Phantom, My Life as a Teenage Robot, Transformers: Animated, Drawn Together, Gargoyles, W.I.T.C.H., and Puppy Dog Pals.
In live-action, she is known for playing Winifred "Freddie" Brooks in the NBC sitcom A Different World
(1987–1993) and librarian Rosalyn Inez in the ABC sitcom Abbott Elementary since 2024.
The tone is emotional and intense.